It finally happened.  Wizards fixed those
two broken cards from Modern Horizons 3,
and sadly, I'm not referring to Nadu
or Ocelot Pride.  For those who didn't
see my previous video, basically,
Wheel of Potential and Suppression Ray
were worded in such a way that
you could choose a number for X,
any number.  Then you had the
option to pay or not that
energy cost and, due to the wording of the
second paragraph, you got the
result of X regardless of whether you paid
or not.  Now, this isn't the video to
get technical and discuss whether
or not that could be done.  They are free to
go back to the previous video on this
topic and do it there.  Regardless
of whether they believe they can be played that way or
not, Wizards recently issued an
errata for both cards.  Wheel of
Potential now says you get three
energy meters and then you can
pay for any amount of energy.
Each player can exile their hand and
draw cards equal to the amount of
energy paid in this way.  If
seven or more energy were paid,
you can play the cards you have
exiled in this way until the end
of your next turn.  And Suppression Ray
now says: "Tap all creatures
target player controls.
You may pay any amount of
energy. If you do, choose up to that
many creatures tapped
this way and put a
stun counter on each one."  Each
card now checks if you actually
paid energy to get the
additional effect, aligning them with
virtually any other card that
requires energy payment.  So,
no stealing your entire deck for just
three mana.  What do you think of this
update? Are there any other cards
that need an errata?  As
always, if you learned something,
like the video and subscribe, because
otherwise I'll make sure Wizards
never fixes Neheb.  Thanks for watching
the video and see you in the next one.